你不知道为何被带到这里 对吧
You don't even know why you're here, do you?
我本不想伤害你
I didn't mean you no harm.
我放低了枪
I lowered my gun,
你却举高了枪
but you raised yours.
你刚才太混蛋了
You were an asshole out there,
就像在亚特兰大的天台上一样
just like you were on that rooftop back there in Atlanta.
你们遗弃我 不顾我死活
What y'all did, leaving me up there…
人都不会那样对一个动物
people wouldn't do that to an animal.
我们回去找过你
We went back for you.
你们还真贴心
Ain't you thoughtful?
真的 我们全去了
We did, all of us…
瑞克 达里尔 T仔
Rick, Daryl, T-Dog.
T仔
Mm, T-Dog.
大块头黑小伙
Yeah, big ol' spear-chucker,
我央求过他
the one I was pleading with.
他却弄掉了钥匙
Mm-hmm, the one that dropped the key.
告诉我他在哪里
Tell me where he's at.
T仔肯定希望和解
I'm sure T-Dog would like to bury the hatchet,
既往不咎嘛
let bygones be bygones.
他没能活下来
He didn't make it.
那我希望他死得很惨
Well, I hope he went slow.
没错
Yeah.
其他人呢
How about the rest?
我弟弟呢
How about my baby brother?
你说他活着
You can't tell me he's alive.
却不告诉我他在哪儿
and then hold off on where he is.
不说是吗
No?
也许那个乡村女会告诉我
Well, maybe the farmer's daughter will help me out.
告诉我
Tell me something…
当她害怕时
when she's scared.
抱紧你时
and she's holding you close,
她颤抖的肌肤
and her trembling skin.
贴着你
is close to you,
软唇相吻
her soft lips are touching you.
这里 吻遍这里
here, all over here,
还有这里
and over here…
感觉很棒 不是吗
feels good, don't it?
我记得你
I remember you.
没错
Yeah.
你独身潜入城市 心理素质很好
You're the sneaky one, the one with nerve.
你啥都不怕 不是吗
You don't scare easy, do you?
我喜欢
I like that.
现在
Now…
我想知道我弟弟在哪儿
I wanna know where my brother is.
我想知道警长在哪儿
I wanna know where the sheriff is.
见鬼
Ah! God!
舒服不
Yeah.
我要知道他们躲在哪里
Now, I wanna know where they're hiding,
你们的营地在哪里
where your camp is,
我现在就要知道
and I wanna know now.
现在
I wanna know now!
他们到底在哪 快说
Where the hell are they? Tell me.
《行尸走肉》
我们要帮她吗
Should we help her?
卡尔
Carl!
见鬼
Shit.
她被咬了吗
Is she bit?
是枪伤
Gunshot.
卡尔 去拿张毯子
Carl, get a blanket.
贝丝 准备好水和毛巾
Beth, water and a towel.
这里吗
Here?
她不能去我们的囚室
She's not coming in the cell blocks.
好的 躺好了
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Steady now.
好了
All right.
好的谢谢
All righ Thank you.
没事了 没事了
It's all right. It's all right.
看着我
Hey, hey, look at me. Look at me.
你是谁
Who are you?
没事了
Hey, it's all right.
听着 别
Hey. Look. Hey.
我们不会伤害你的
No. We're not going to hurt you.
除非你想做傻事 明白吗
unless you try something stupid first, all right?
瑞克
Rick.
这是谁
Who the hell is this?
告诉我们你的名字
You wanna tell us your name?
你的名字
你们过来看一下
You all come on in here.
怎么了
Everything all right?
你看了就明白了
You're gonna wanna see this.
我们走 卡尔 拿上包
Go ahead. Carl, take the bag.
我们会替你保管好武器
We'll keep this safe and sound.
这里的门都锁上了 你很安全
The doors are all locked. You'll be safe here.
我们会治好你的伤
And we can treat that.
我可没要你们救我
I didn't ask for your help.
无所谓
Doesn't matter.
不能让你随便离开
Can't let you leave.
天啊
Oh, God.
感谢上帝
Thank God. Thank God.
Thank God.
你怎么办到的
How?
一个人撑下来
Solitary.
她一路坚持 躲到了一个囚室里
Poor thing fought her way into a cell.
一定是脱水昏了过去
Must have passed out. Dehydrated.
对不起
I'm sorry.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
一切都还好吗
Everything all right?
我来告诉你一声 科尔曼先生准备好了
I just came to tell you. Mr. Coleman, he's ready.
知道了 我去实验室找你
Okay, I'll meet you in the lab.
遵命
Yes, sir.
真抱歉
Sorry about that.
没关系
No problem.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
实际上我现在就需要你的帮助
Actually, I could use your help with something now.
我说了我会回来的
I said I'll be back.
不
No.
这可不是小事
I wish it were just that.
我们能给你治伤
We can tend to that wound for you,
给你些食物和水
give you a little food and water,
然后就送你走
and then send you on your way.
但你必须告诉我们 你是怎么找到这里的
But you're gonna have to tell us how you found us.
还有为什么你带着奶粉
and why you were carrying formula.
那些补给是一位亚裔男孩和一漂亮姑娘
The supplies were dropped by a young Asian guy.
丢下的
with a pretty girl.
发生了什么事
What happened?
他们被袭击了吗
Were they attacked?
- 他们被带走了 - 谁带走的
- They were taken. - Taken? By who?
就是那个开枪打我的狗娘养的
By the same son of a bitch who shot me.
听着 他们是我们的人
Hey, these are our people.
你马上告诉我发生了什么
You tell us what happened now!
你不许再碰我一下
Don't you ever touch me again!
你还是说出来吧
You'd better start talking.
你面临的问题比枪伤严重多了
You're gonna have a much bigger problem than a gunshot wound.
自己去找啊
Find 'em yourself.
放松 放松 放下
Hey, shh, shh, shh. Put it down.
你来这里肯定是想帮我们
You came here for a reason.
有个小镇
There's a town.
叫伍德伯里
Woodbury.
大概有75名幸存者
About 75 survivors.
我认为他们被带到那里了
I think they were taken there.
一整个小镇吗
A whole town?
一个自称总督的人管着这个小镇
It's run by this guy who calls himself the Governor…
帅气 有魅力 像个邪教头头
pretty boy, charming, Jim Jones type.
他有手下吗
He got muscle?
一支自封的准军事部队
Paramilitary wannabes.
四周围墙上他们都派人持枪巡逻
They have armed sentries on every wall.
你知道怎么进去吗
You know a way in?
那地方行尸进不去
The place is secure from walkers,
但活人能溜进去
but we could slip our way through.
你怎么知道我们的位置
How'd you know how to get here?
他们提到过一所监狱
They mentioned a prison,
说了它在哪个方向
said which direction it was in,
直走就到
that it was a straight shot.
这是赫谢尔
This is Hershel,
那个被带走女孩的父亲
the father of the girl who was taken.
他会给你处理伤口
He'll take care of that.
我必须说声佩服
I gotta hand it to you,
你比我记忆中坚强多了
a lot tougher than I remember.
难怪你能活到现在
No surprise you lasted this long.
按照「好好警官」的作风
Should I figured the way Officer Friendly abandoned people?
他应该早就把你抛弃了
He would have left you behind by now.
但是他没那么做 是吧
But he didn't do that, did he?
那告诉我 你们都住在哪儿
Hmm. So tell me, where y'all been at?
他们找来只是时间问题
It's just a matter of time before they come looking.
我会烤个粉红糖霜蛋糕迎接他们
I'll bake a cake with pink frosting.
他们会喜欢吗
Would they like that?
没人会来的
Ain't nobody coming.
瑞克会的
Rick is.
- 等他来到这里 - 他什么也做不了
- And when he gets here… - He's gonna do nothing,
他救不走你和你的小宝贝的
not if he wants you and Bo Peep back.
你以为就我一人在这里呢
Think I'm in this by myself?
你对付不了我们
You can't take us all.
我们人可多着呢
There's too many of us.
你们那群孬种 能有几个真汉子
There ain't a pair of nuts between the whole pussy lot of you.
我们一直在外面拼杀
We've been on the road,
而不是躲在地牢里
not hiding in some dungeon.
我们有瑞克 肖恩 戴尔
Rick, Shane, Dale,
吉姆 安德莉亚
Jim, Andrea.
是吗
Really?
真的吗
Is that right?
谢谢你
Thank you.
你怎么知道我们可以信任她
How do you know we can trust her?
事关玛姬和格伦 还有什么好争的
This is Maggie and Glenn. Why are we even debating?
不争了 我去找他们
We ain't. I'll go after them.
这个地方听起来戒备森严
Well, this place sounds pretty secure.
- 你不能独自去 - 我也去
- You can't go alone. - I'll go.
我也去
Me, too.
算我一个
I'm in.
我带了闪光弹和催泪弹
I got the flash bangs and I got the tear gas.
说不定会派上用场
You never know what you're gonna need.
别担心你老爸
Hey, don't you worry about your old man.
我会保护他的
I'm gonna keep my eye on him.
- 这儿以前不是行尸成堆吗 - 原来是
- Wasn't this place overrun? - It was.
你们靠自己清理光的吗
And you cleared it out all by yourselves?
就你们几个
Just the few of you?
原本还有其他人
There were others.
卡尔
Carl.
- 你对你妈妈做的事 - 我必须那么做
- What you did for Mom… - I had to.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I… I know.
我懂 对此我很抱歉
I know, and I'm sorry.
这不是一般人可以做到的
No one should have to go through that.
你要去多久
How long will you be gone?
听着 如果我们走后发生了任何事
Look, if something happens while we're gone…
我们会没事的
We'll be all right.
若发生什么事
If anything happens,
你就把大家锁在牢房里 保证他们的安全
you get everyone locked in the cells, keep them all safe.
- 我会的 - 我知道
- I will. - I know.
我知道你可以的
I know you will.
照顾好你妹妹 好吗
Take care of your sister, all right?
达里尔一直管她叫小拽女
Daryl's been calling her Ass-Kicker.
小拽女
Ass-Kicker?
这就叫上了
Has he, now?
我一直在想 我们该叫她什么
I've been thinking, what should we really call her?
你有什么想法
What do you think?
还记得我上三年级时的老师 米勒女士吗
Remember my third grade teacher, Mrs. Mueller?
当然
Of course.
她的名字叫朱迪思
Her first name was Judith.
你觉得那个名字怎么样
Do you think that's a good name?
我觉得这是个好名字
I think that's… that's a fine name.
就叫朱迪思吧
Judith it is.
注意安全
Stay safe.
我命硬着呢 记得吗
Nine lives, remember?
把他们带回来
Bring them back.
科尔曼先生
Mr. Coleman,
这是安德莉亚
this is Andrea.
米尔顿会告诉你怎么做
Milton will bring you up to speed.
晚饭时见
I'll see you for dinner.
多谢了
Thank you for this.
你算帮了我们一个大忙
You're doing us a great service.
那么 你到底在…
So, what exactly are you…?
帮忙把唱片调到曲目一
Could you cue up the first song on the record?
当然
Sure.
听我指令
On my mark.
我叫米尔顿·马梅
My name is Milton Mamet.
如果以下的叙述属实
Please raise your right hand off the bed.
请举起你的右手
if you recognize any of the following statements to be true.
你叫迈克尔·科尔曼
Your name is Michael Coleman.
你妻子是贝蒂·科尔曼
You were married to Betty Coleman.
你的孩子叫小迈克尔和艾米丽
Your children were Michael Jr. And Emily.
很好
Very good.
他说什么
What did he say?
他问在等候时 能不能让音乐一直放着
He asked if I could keep it playing while we wait.
好了 你也来体会一下
All righty, I want you to imagine.
我当时在天台拼命求生是什么感觉
how I felt fighting my way off that roof…
就一只手
one hand,
血流不止
losing blood,
行尸们龇牙咧嘴 向我步步逼近
walkers chomping down at me every step of the way.
最后一次机会 你队伍在哪里
Last chance. Where's your group?
不说是吧
All right.
请便吧
Suit yourself.
你对它来说算一道大餐
You're a pretty big snack for this fella.
不过人们常说
But you know what they say…
「中餐好吃不顶饱」
he's gonna be hungry again in an hour.
开饭了 伙计
Go! Run, boy!
科尔曼先生一死 我们就把他绑住
After Mr. Coleman passes, we'll restrain him.
然后他会变成行尸
He'll reanimate.
我会再问一遍问题 记录下他的回应
I'll ask the questions again, record his responses.
你负责终结他的行尸形态
I need you to end the subject's reanimated state.
好的
All right.
我一直致力于研究
I've been trying to determine whether.
当人变成行尸后是否还具有
trace memory and human consciousness exist.
记忆痕迹和人性意识
after the subject has transformed,
但到目前为止 还没有基准样本
but I had no baseline to work off of.
可供参考
till now.
他患有前列腺癌
Prostate cancer.
以我们的医疗设备救不了他
We didn't have the resources to treat him,
所以他自愿献身作试验样本
so he volunteered to be the test subject.
他一直都十分配合
He's been very cooperative.
是个非常好的人
He's a remarkable man.
你们很熟吗
You're close?
我们这样呆在一起好长时间了
We spent a lot of time together.
放着的歌曲 手中的颂钵 这些问题
The song, the singing bowl, the questions…
已经重复了几十遍了
we've done that a few dozen times.
他死后 这些信息在他潜意识里
These are cues that will hopefully linger.
依然有可能残存
in his unconscious mind even after he's died.
根本就没有什么潜意识 米尔顿
There is no unconscious mind, Milton.
等他们醒来 就成怪物了
When they turn, they become monsters.
仅此而已
That's all.
之前的他们已不复存在了
Whoever they once were is gone.
我们走着瞧
We'll see.
你之前从没经历过这个吧
You haven't seen this before, have you?
转变的过程
The transformation.
没有
No.
你家里没人变成…
No one in your family was…?
我是独生子
I'm an only child.
小时候我父母就去世了
My parents died when I was young.
事态变糟糕那会儿你也是一个人吗
Weren't you with anyone when everything went down?
我那会远程办公
I telecommuted to work.
我其实从来没…
I never really…
他们认识安德莉亚
So, they know Andrea.
但他们不知道她在这儿
But they don't know she's here.
但他们认识你弟弟
But they do know your brother.
那男孩认识
He does.
可女孩我就不清楚了
But I don't know about her.
之前没见过她
I've never seen her before.
他们的人会来救他俩的
Their people may come for 'em.
可能吧
Maybe.
安德莉亚和那男孩都说他们回去找过我
The kid and Andrea both say they went back for me.
那又如何 他死活不松口
So what? He won't break,
不说他们人在哪儿
say where his people are?
真是个顽强的小杂种
He's a tough son of a bitch.
几分钟就把那行尸干掉了
Picked that walker apart in minutes.
看来野外拼杀了一冬天 这小子有点男人样了
Maybe a winter in the sticks put some hair on his balls.
他们人来了我们需要用他做人质
We'll need him for leverage if his people come.
为什么要杀他
What you try to kill him for?
- 看他就不顺眼 - 那姑娘说什么
- He pissed me off. - What's the girl say?
我下一个就打算找她谈
I was just about to go talk to her next.
还是让我来吧
I'll take care of it.
能坐下吗
May I?
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们会把你送回给你们的人
We'll take you back to your people,
并解释这一切只是误会
explain this was all just a misunderstanding.
你告诉我们他们在哪儿 我们送你回去
You tell us where they are and we'll drive you there.
我要跟格伦说话
I want to talk to Glenn.
这可不行
I can't allow that.
你们的人很危险
Your people are dangerous.
把我们的人铐在天台
Handcuffed my man to a roof,
逼着他自行截肢
forced him to amputate his own hand.
我可不知道那些事儿
I don't know anything about that.
你只需坦白他们在哪儿
You just tell us where they are.
我们就把他们带来
and we'll bring them here.
你很安全 我保证
You'll be safe, I promise.
不说
No?
那好
Fine.
敬酒不吃吃罚酒
Let's try something else.
请起立
Stand up, please.
起立
Stand up.
脱掉你的上衣
Take off your shirt.
不
No.
脱掉你的上衣
Take off your shirt.
否则我剁下格伦的一只手给你送来
or I'll bring Glenn's hand in here.
继续啊
Go on.
还不说吗
So you gonna talk?
你想干什么 就请自便吧
You can do whatever you're gonna do.
下地狱去吧
And go to hell.
他们有巡逻队
They have patrols.
我们还是走过去吧
We're better off on foot.
有多远 天马上就黑了
How far? Night's coming.
一或两英里的样子
It's a mile, maybe two.
你为我和我孩子所做的一切
You know, what you did for me,
当我还在…
for my baby, while I was…
整理思绪时…
working things out…
谢谢
Thank you.
伙伴就该这样
It's what we do.
- 瑞克 - 蹲下
- Rick. - Down.
保持战术阵型 别开火
Formation. No gunfire.
奥斯卡
Oscar.
实在是太多了
There's too many of them.
这边走
This way.
去那里 快跟上
Through there. Come on.
把门关上
Get the door.
别出声 别出声
Keep it down. Keep it down.
这味道 真冲
The smell, it's loud.
这他妈是什么东西
What the hell is that?
是狐狸或什么动物的遗体
It's got to be a fox or what's left of one.
看来忠犬拼了命救主
I guess Lassie went home.
- 你们他妈是谁 - 我们没有恶意
- Ah! Who the hell are you? - We don't mean any harm.
- 快从我家滚出去 - 好的
- Get outta my house! - Okay, okay, okay.
我们会走的 但现在走不了
We will, but we can't right now.
- 快滚 - 让他闭嘴
- Now! - Shut him up.
现在就给我滚
Get out right now!
外面有一堆行尸
There are walkers outside.
- 我要报警 - 我就是警察
- I'll call the cops! - I am a cop.
现在请你把枪放下
Now I need you to lower the gun.
千万别鲁莽行事
Don't do anything rash.
一切好说 咱们
Everything's fine. Let's just…
和和气气地放下枪 好吗
let's just take this nice and slow, okay?
看着我
Look at me.
我要看你的警徽
Show me your badge.
好的 在我口袋里
All right. It's in my pocket. It's in my pocket.
让我慢慢伸手去拿
Now, I'm just gonna reach down nice and slow.
放开 快放开我
Let go! Let go of me!
我要杀了你
I'll kill you, you.
放开我
let go of me!
闭嘴 闭嘴
Shut up! Shut up!
救命啊 他们发现我了
Help! They found me!
- 救命 - 别开门
- Help me! - Don't open that door.
四面楚歌啊
Remember the Alamo?
达里尔 准备开门
Daryl, help me with the door.
你们不是真要这么做吧
You've gotta be kidding.
他已经死了 去后门看看
He's dead. Check the back.
后门安全
It's clear.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
开始了
It's happening.
我叫米尔顿·马梅
My name is Milton Mamet.
如果以下的叙述属实
Please raise your right hand off the bed.
请举起你的右手
if you recognize any of the following statements to be true.
你叫迈克尔·科尔曼
Your name is Michael Coleman.
你妻子是贝蒂·科尔曼
You were married to Betty Coleman.
你的孩子叫小迈克尔和艾米丽
Your children were Michael Jr. And Emily.
看见没 他有反应了
Did you see that? He responded.
手指动一动 说明不了什么
Their fingers move. That could be anything.
他手被绑着 所以举不起来
No, he can't raise his hand. It's the angle.
给他松开让我再试一次
I want to try again without the restraints.
- 不行 - 我们说不定已经触及他的意识了
- No. - We may have tethered his consciousness.
- 必须要试试 - 不行
- We have to try. - No.
我知道这会有危险
I know what happens if the subject comes for us.
要你来就是保护我
That's what you're here for.
一旦解开束缚 它就会攻击你
As soon as we pull the restraints, he'll lunge.
我叫米尔顿·马梅
My name is Milton Mamet.
请举起你的右手
Please raise your right hand…
我想趁热打铁
I think I'd like to record my findings.
记录实验结果
while they're fresh.
放下武器
Drop it.
小打小闹到此结束
We're through with games.
你们中一人必须说出营地位置
Now one of you is gonna give up your camp.
监狱
The prison.
努内兹附近那个吗
The one near Nunez?
那地方被行尸占据了
That place is overrun.
我们攻下了那里
We took it.
- 你们有多少人 - 十人
- How many are you? - 10.
现在还剩十人
We have 10 now.
仅靠十人清理掉了整个监狱的行尸
10 people cleared that whole prison of biters?
没事的
Shh, shh, shh. It's all right.
没事了
It's all right.
仅靠十人
10 people.
那在危险区
That's deep in the red zone.
- 十个人不可能… - 她在撒谎吗
- There's no way only 10… - So she's lying?
如果她撒谎 那么就有一大队人
'Cause if she's lying, that means a pretty sizeable force.
在我们附近
has moved into our backyard.
但如果她没撒谎
But if she's not,
你弟弟的这群人马
this group with your brother at its core.
完成了不可能完成的任务
has done something you told me couldn't be done.
他们做到了
They did it.
你弟弟说不定正在外面 搜寻他们
Your brother might be out there right now, searching for them.
常言道「血浓于水」
Blood is blood, right?
我很好奇你会忠于哪边
Makes me wonder where your loyalties lie.
我忠于这里
Here.
你俩带一小队人去侦查监狱
You two get a small group and scout this prison.
我要知道对方的底细
I want to know exactly what we're dealing with.
好的 立刻去办
Yeah. You got it.
你遵守诺言
You kept your word.
又回来了
that you'd be back.
米尔顿那边还好吗
Everything go all right with Milton?
发生了什么
What happened?
科尔曼先生死了
Mr. Coleman died.
米尔顿找到想找的东西了吗
And did Milton find what he was looking for?
没有
No.
没事的 没事了
It's all right. It's all right.
都结束了
It's over now, huh?
没事的
It's all right.